[Music]
hello and welcome this is stocks to
watch on bloomberg queen
i am vaquero this is where we take you
through three stocks which are in the
news
and take them up with our experts uh but
today
the stocks that we are going to talk
about is uh hdfc bank
on the back of earnings and again on the
back of earnings i see i sell lombard
and gic and vodafone idea well we do
have a lot of updates in the telecom
communications sector
and to take us through some of these
talks we are in conversation with
avinash korakshakar
the director of research at profit part
securities who's joining us
on this like at this point in time but
before i go across global enough let's
take up the first stock and that's
hdfc bank uh we've had earnings and it's
actually been uh you know
business as usual it seems like for hdfc
bank because
we're looking at a near 18 growth in its
net interest income for the first
quarter
year on year and its net profit has
risen around 20
i'm sure uh at the on the base of it a
lot of will be
curious about the provisioning that
stands at around a little less than 3
900 crores for the quarter
but that really hasn't dampened uh too
much when it comes to the net profit
which did
grow nearly 20 percent like i said a lot
of this
is business as usual let's get in
avinash into the conversation avinash
good morning and thanks for joining in
uh
uh good morning adam i think uh numbers
presented by
sdfc bank have definitely been quite
robust given the
challenging scenario of a lockdown you
know which we saw in the month of april
and may
uh pleasantly i think you know the
operating profitability as well as the
loan disbursement growth has been solid
in fact the
management commentary in the conference
call indicated that you know
loan disbursements are now to almost 80
percent of the pre-corvette levels
and the bank is quite confident that the
second half should be equally better
i think the only near-term concern could
be the slippage number
which i would say that you know in all
probability uh on the unsecured book
could possibly get elevated maybe in the
second half
so all said and done numbers are
definitely a decent set of numbers
uh i would be uh definitely be sure that
today the markets could possibly
give it a thumbs up in today's morning
session and i think overall you know the
management commentary on the management
transition
plus other uh you know sticky issues
like the anti-core deal
have also been uh you know correctly and
uh you know
very rightly uh you know you know
commented by the management so all said
and done a pretty it's a decent set of
numbers and i think
one could definitely look at it you know
from a long term point of view
uh today the stock may open higher but
any decline should be used as an
opportunity to accumulate the stock
fair enough on to the next
uh well you know stock on our lesson
lombard general insurance and this is
where we've seen
gross premium decline by five percent
on a year-on-year basis at a little less
than around thirty four hundred crores
it's netting
income is up around twenty eight percent
at three ninety acros
uh we all know that uh some of these
insurance companies have had
challenges with respect to collecting
premiums uh
well based on the factors that we've
seen in icsa lombard
and your general outlook for the company
what's the way forward here i think
numbers presented were definitely much
better than the street expectations in
fact uh markets were expecting that the
cross
premiums in this quarter could
definitely show a negative sign
uh considering the fact that you know
big users like the automobile sector has
actually shown a significant degrowth in
this period
our sense is the net income has actually
gone up largely because of
some sort of increase on the treasury
side but operationally you know i would
believe that at least for the next one
quarter
business will continue to be challenging
and i think from a longer term
perspective any strong recovery can be
expected
only from the start of the third quarter
or f by 21.
uh we believe that you know any weakness
again should be used as an opportunity
to accumulate the stock
longer term prospects are definitely
good but fi 21 will continue to be
challenging and i don't i won't be
surprised
that the second quarter also you know
gross premiums may not show a kind of a
positive trajectory we could see a
better number coming only in the second
half
so net net continue to hold on and i
would believe it's a good long term kind
of
addition to the portfolio when we move
on to vodafone
quite volatile though it has come off
its
recent lows that is about 12 rupees
per share mark it's currently around you
know nine rupees odd
uh in the latest in terms of news what
we understand is that it's paid about
another thousand crores to the
department of telecom
communications towards its agr news
6 across in three branches
so slowly and steadily vodafone is
certainly getting uh
you know and uh
well we do have another matter coming up
in the course today when it comes to
egr2 specifically
uh that telecom sector in general will
be in focus but are we not sure
let's talk about vodafone idea uh how do
you
rate the stock at this point in time
would you want to go ahead and risk
uh considering the stock is near its uh
life flow
uh i think this news flow about uh
you know vodafone paying its jews on the
agr front is definitely a positive
sentimental booster to the
i think we do have a problem
but you know mentioning uh earlier that
uh
when it comes to warfarin idea uh well
we've seen
okay i think we have um yes
now i was saying that uh this uh news
flow about agr payments made by vodafone
is definitely a
positive sentiment booster to the stock
in the near term uh we could see a
short-term upside in the stock you know
because most of the negatives are
factored in
but i think the real re-rating for this
stock could come in again only when
operational metrics improve and i think
that is
definitely a long way ahead uh they have
just paid 7000 odd close for the
agr dues and a lot of uh remaining dues
are still unpaid
the markets would be obviously looking
at uh some sort of
uh you know improvement on the cash
flows and on the operating uh ebitda
front
uh fourth quarter has been good but i
would believe that you know from a
longer term perspective it is still
better to
keep a wait and watch here on the short
term yes the stock could show a decent
upside today
but longer term i think all depends on
the operational metrics
how quickly they turn around and get
these numbers so i would believe you
know short-term traders could definitely
uh you know take the benefit of the news
flow today but longer-term investors
should actually
stay away from this stock for some time
okay
and even by asking abinash about
you know large e-commerce players
especially from the b2b space and
within this space we like a company
called india mart our sense is that
uh you know this quarter also we could
see a very strong
top line growth of at least uh 20 25 and
operating profitability uh
is definitely also going to get a
significant booster
overall i would believe that uh you know
despite the fact that the lockdown
happened in april may
business was as usual for india mart and
considering the kind of cash flows and
the kind of
uh you know asset light kind of business
which they run
i would not be surprised that we could
see a decent 25 to 26 percent earnings
growth for fy21 so
you know this is a stock which one
should accumulate for a longer term
point of view
the stock has been uh trading a little
soft in the past few weeks
so this could be a good opportunity for
you know a good long term acquisition
considering that they are market leaders
in this space and obviously you know at
these levels also there's a decent risk
reward available
right it's it's it's
currently trending around 2000 rupees a
share so it's a very uh interesting
price point as
as well uh for india mark considering it
has seen much higher highs in the past
but we'll be watching after that but on
that note uh avinash karashakar would
like to thank you for joining us and
taking us through your views
on the stocks that we've just discussed
today and that's a wrap on this segment
but that's perlina stay tuned
oh